const phy = [
{
    question: "Unit of force is:",
    options: ["Joule", "Watt", "Newton", "Pascal"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "Newton’s First Law is also called:",
    options: ["Law of inertia", "Law of motion", "Law of gravity", "Law of acceleration"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Work =",
    options: ["Force × Distance", "Mass × Velocity", "Power × Time", "Force / Distance"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Kinetic energy formula is:",
    options: ["½mv²", "mv", "mgh", "F/m"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Acceleration due to gravity is approximately:",
    options: ["10 m/s²", "9.8 m/s²", "8 m/s²", "12 m/s²"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "Frequency is measured in:",
    options: ["Hz", "N", "J", "m/s"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Ohm’s Law is:",
    options: ["V = IR", "P = IV", "F = ma", "E = mc²"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Unit of power is:",
    options: ["Joule", "Watt", "Newton", "Volt"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "Momentum =",
    options: ["mv", "ma", "mgh", "½mv²"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "A wave transfers:",
    options: ["Matter", "Energy", "Mass", "Particles"],
    answer: 1
}
];